oregonscientific.com 2014-07-26

# Oregon Scientific - Smart Living

You are welcome to read and enjoy our site, but there are some limits on what you can do with it. 

This site may contain hot links that will provide you with information or bring you to the web page of a third party. Oregon Scientific has no control over the information that you may receive through such hot links and does not endorse your use of such third party web pages and the information provided thereby. Oregon Scientific is not responsible for: 1) the accuracy, completeness, timeliness, reliability, content or availability of any information received by you as a result of your use of the site; 2) loss or damage to your records or data; or 3) your use of, or results achieved from any information received by you as a result of your use of the site.

Please note that any feedback or suggestions provided to Oregon Scientific shall be deemed non-confidential and shall become the sole property of Oregon Scientific. Oregon Scientific shall be free to use such information on an unrestricted basis.

Any person is hereby authorized to view, copy, print and distribute the contents of Oregon Scientific's web pages for personal, private, noncommercial use subject to the following conditions: (1) You may not re-create any substantial portion of the contents of this site for use with, or as, another site, even if the site is noncommercial in nature; (2) any alteration or modification of the contents is prohibited; and (3)any copy of the contents must include the copyright notice: "Copyright Oregon Scientific 2004. All rights reserved."

Please note that any product, process or technology described in our web pages may be the subject of other intellectual property rights reserved by Oregon Scientific and are not licensed hereunder.

Any comments or materials sent to Oregon Scientific including feedback data, such as questions, comments or suggestions shall be deemed to be non-confidential even if you tell us that you think that they are private and confidential. Oregon Scientific shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, exhibit, display, create derivative works and distribute anything received without restriction or obligation of compensation. Oregon Scientific shall also be free to use any ideas or concepts provided to develop, manufacture and/or market its products.

The published material provided on our web pages is provided "AS IS" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement. In no event shall Oregon Scientific be liable for damages of any kind arising from the use of Oregon Scientific's web pages and Oregon Scientific assumes no responsibility for errors, omissions or faults of any kind in these web pages or any other web pages linked to it. Information on this web site is subject to change without notice.

Oregon Scientific's ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY 

Oregon Scientific is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit Oregon Scientific on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Oregon Scientific. For instance when you provide personal information through Oregon Scientific Contact Us, we use the information on an internal basis only and do not provide it to anyone outside of Oregon Scientific.

Awareness  
Oregon Scientific provides this Online Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy policy, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage.

What we collect  
At the [Oregon Scientific.com](http://www.oregonscientific.com/) web site, you can obtain information about products and services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, email, business contact, address, and demographic information such as age, gender, occupation and education level. Information pertaining to the type of Oregon Scientific product and other related equipment may also be collected. When and where relevant, additional information such as billing information, transaction, and credit card information will be collected when online purchases are made through the oregonscientific.com web sites.

Please note that the information submitted to Oregon Scientific via the web may be processed or stored outside of the country where it was submitted.

How we use it  
Oregon Scientific uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize our web sites for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with information we think would be of particular interest. We will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct information or market research contact.

Third Party Operators  
Please note that certain areas of our web site may be operated by third parties. Whenever this is the case, please refer to the privacy statement of the third party to understand how your personally identifiable information is treated by that party.

Choice  
Oregon Scientific will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct information from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests.

Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.

Accuracy & Access  
Oregon Scientific strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable efforts to provide you with online access to your registration data so that you may view, update or correct your information at the Oregon Scientific site where it was submitted. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. To access your personally identifiable information, return to the web page where you originally entered it and follow the instructions on that web page.

Links to Third Party Web Sites  
Links to third party web sites on the site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Oregon Scientific site. Oregon Scientific has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. Thus, Oregon Scientific does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so at your own risk. 

Security  
Oregon Scientific is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Oversight  
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [info@oregonscientific.com](mailto:info@oregonscientific.com)

Children's Privacy Protection  
Oregon Scientific takes special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourages parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities and interests. [Oregon Scientific.com](http://www.oregonscientific.com/) is a general audience web site.

When a child under the age of 13 attempts to provide information to Oregon Scientific, we ask that they have a parent or Guardian provide their consent first. This is done by emailing the parent or Guardian a notice which details: 

  1. Who is collecting the information;   

  2. What information is being collected;   

  3. The purpose behind the collection of the information; and   

  4. The parent's choices regarding the collection and use of the information.   

  5. We will only collect information from children under the age of thirteen once we receive parental consent. We do not share any information collected from children under the age of 13 with third parties.

If a parent provides his or her consent for their child to disclose information to Oregon Scientific, that parent may at any time review the information, ask to have it deleted or refuse to allow further collection. These requests should be made by emailing at the following email address: [info@oregonscientific.com](mailto:info@oregonscientific.com).

Oregon Scientific may collect personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and the like, for registration purposes for services such as the Oregon Scientific service or for promotions and contests. In the case of online promotions and other activities, we do not condition a child's participation on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. The information is not disclosed to anyone outside of Oregon Scientific and is stored in a secure environment.

How Oregon Scientific uses cookies  
A cookie is a piece of text to be placed on your computer's hard drive. If you are general user browsing our web site, no cookies will be placed on your hard drive. For users who log in to our web site , cookie will then be applied. However, when you quit your browser or log out from our web site, cookies will be erased completely from your hard drive. Cookies help us to deliver information specific to your interests, to eliminate the need to re-enter your password , or to keep track of your shopping cart. We do not follow your browsing path outside of the Oregon Scientific site. Please note that certain areas of our web site may be operated by third parties, in which case you should refer to that parties' web site for information on how they use cookies.
